<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cmpsoares</title>
    <link>http://www.cmpsoares.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on cmpsoares</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 07:31:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.cmpsoares.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Something&#39;s coming soon</title>
      <link>http://www.cmpsoares.com/posts/something-coming-soon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 07:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.cmpsoares.com/posts/something-coming-soon/</guid>
      <description>Well I always dreamed of creating a blog, writing my own technical endeavorements for other technician, engineers and curious minds to read. However, I must say it has been my most procrastinated goal ever. But after getting a taste of it at my last job (unfortunatelly it wasn&amp;rsquo;t publicly available) I believe this time it will be it.
So I&amp;rsquo;ll see you soon with hopefully with content that&amp;rsquo;d you&amp;rsquo;ll love or find of great use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>http://www.cmpsoares.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.cmpsoares.com/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a Curious Automation Hacker &amp;amp; Versatile Site Reliability and Big Data Engineer currently living in Lisboa, Portugal. Born in the Netherlands and raised with the traits and benefits of a multicultural education, which made me a very inquisitive Computer Science Engineer and a technology enthusiast.
My professional interests range from SRE, Monitoring, Analytics, Automation, Big Data, Distributed System to Datahub and Microservice Platform Architectures, including the many tools and programming languages that are related to it (i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CMPSOARES Comment Policy</title>
      <link>http://www.cmpsoares.com/cmpsoares-comment-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.cmpsoares.com/cmpsoares-comment-policy/</guid>
      <description>We want you to feel at home when you post a comment on CMPSOARES. We want everyone to feel at home posting comments on CMPSOARES. We don’t know what your home is like, but we know how we expect people to behave when they visit ours. That’s why we reserve the right to delete comments and ban users as needed to keep the comment threads here civil and substantive.
Our No.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://www.cmpsoares.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.cmpsoares.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>Hello,
If you want to reach out to me for work related topics, ask for some insights or for a cup of coffee or beer, feel free to reach out to using social media or shoot me an email to contact[at]cmpsoares.com.
I hope to develop a sort of contact form in the near future, but it&amp;rsquo;s still on the TODO List. ;-)
Hope to hear from you soon.
Carlos Soares.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>http://www.cmpsoares.com/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.cmpsoares.com/projects/</guid>
      <description>Nothing to see here&amp;hellip; Move along!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>