<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>CMPSOARES | CMPSOARES</title><link>https://cmpsoares.com/</link><description>CMPSOARES | CMPSOARES</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 07:31:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cmpsoares.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://cmpsoares.com/about/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 07:31:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cmpsoares.com/about/</guid><description>&lt;p>I am a Curious Automation Hacker &amp;amp; Versatile Site Reliability and Big Data Engineer currently living in Lisboa, Portugal. Born in the Netherlands and raised with the traits and benefits of a multicultural education, which made me a very inquisitive Computer Science Engineer and a technology enthusiast.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>My professional interests range from SRE, Monitoring, Analytics, Automation, Big Data, Distributed System to Datahub and Microservice Platform Architectures, including the many tools and programming languages that are related to it (i.e. Docker, Kafka, Elasticsearch, Cassandra, Python, Node.JS, Java, Go, etc.). Casually, I also like reading about other innovation-related subjects such as Artificial Intelligence, Cryptocurrencies, Blockchain and of course the latest Startups.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in getting to know me better, feel free to &lt;a href="https://www.dropbox.com/s/e2z6evmi4jawbx5/English%20CV%20-%20Carlos%20Soares%20Traditional%20vLatest.pdf?dl=1" target="_blank">download my CV&lt;/a> or reach out to me using one of the available contacts.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>CMPSOARES Comment Policy</title><link>https://cmpsoares.com/cmpsoares-comment-policy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 07:31:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cmpsoares.com/cmpsoares-comment-policy/</guid><description>&lt;p>We want you to feel at home when you post a comment on CMPSOARES. We want everyone to feel at home posting comments on CMPSOARES. We don’t know what your home is like, but we know how we expect people to behave when they visit ours. That’s why we reserve the right to delete comments and ban users as needed to keep the comment threads here civil and substantive.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Our No. 1 house rule is simple: &lt;strong>Don’t be a jerk&lt;/strong>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Want to be the kind of commenter we’d love to bring home to Thanksgiving dinner? Here’s what we like to see in comments:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Weigh in with smart, informed ideas that contribute further to the story.&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Give us useful, constructive criticism.&lt;/strong> Spot a typo or an error? Let us know and we will correct it.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Demonstrate and share the intelligence, wisdom, and humour we know you possess.&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Don’t feed the trolls.&lt;/strong> You wouldn’t dive into a debate with our ill-informed, weird uncle Gary just for the heck of it. And you definitely wouldn’t feed him. (We told you he was weird.) Downvote and flag these comments instead.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Although we can’t be everywhere at once, here are some of the kinds of comments we’re going to do our best to curtail:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Promoting your own brand, product, or blog.&lt;/strong> So you’ve got a climate change solution that will simultaneously solve world poverty. Great. Send it through our contact form, you Elon Musk, you.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Impersonating authors or other commenters.&lt;/strong> We can’t believe we have to say this, but: Don’t do that. It’s weird.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Comments that make it clear you didn’t read the article.&lt;/strong> Enraged that we didn’t mention X in a story about Y? Slow down, Speedy McFingerson. If you’d made it past paragraph two, you’d see a very well thought-out discussion of that X you hold so dear.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Comments that are completely out of left field.&lt;/strong> Sometimes discussions veer off a bit but are still related to the original subject. That is fine. Hijacking the conversation to promote off-topic commentary is not.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Threats — no matter how vague — against the author or other commenters.&lt;/strong> Things can get heated. Before you casually mention your foe’s home address, think of your Mother Earth. (Bonus points if you never use the phrase “Mother Earth.”)&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Racism, sexism, homophobia, you get the drift.&lt;/strong> Call us the PC Police, fine, but don’t say we didn’t warn you when you get tased. **And by tased, we mean banned or deleted. CMPSOARES.com has not — and will not — ever own a taser, and even if we were to own a solar-charged taser, we’d be too scared to use it.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Trolling.&lt;/strong> If you’re a climate denier just out for a good trolling and are not contributing meaningfully to the conversation, we’ll be pushing you back under the bridge.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>&lt;em>Note that we did not write this amazing comment policy all by ourselves, we were inspired and copied part of it from the amazing policy from &lt;a href="https://grist.org/grist-comment-policy/" target="_blank">Grist&lt;/a>. Always give credit where it&amp;rsquo;s due.&lt;/em>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://cmpsoares.com/contact/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 07:31:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cmpsoares.com/contact/</guid><description>&lt;p>Hello,&lt;/p>
&lt;p>If you want to reach out to me for work-related topics, ask for some insights or for a cup of coffee or beer, feel free to reach out to using social media or shoot me an email to &lt;code>contact[at]cmpsoares.com&lt;/code>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I hope to develop a sort of contact form in the near future, but it&amp;rsquo;s still on the TODO List. ;-)&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Hope to hear from you soon.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Carlos Soares.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Posts</title><link>https://cmpsoares.com/posts/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 07:31:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cmpsoares.com/posts/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://cmpsoares.com/projects/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 07:31:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cmpsoares.com/projects/</guid><description>&lt;p>Nothing to see here yet&amp;hellip; Move along!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Justing adding a test adsense script below:&lt;/p>
&lt;!--adsense--></description></item></channel></rss>